{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929651699","data":{"timestamp":" 946929651699"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bdecb37d-7621-416f-ab47-f4e83d3602b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929674871","data":{"timestamp":" 946929674870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bdecb37d-7621-416f-ab47-f4e83d3602b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929687602","data":{"timestamp":" 946929687602"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bcdd7488-04fd-42c5-a803-0031de85a84b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929688665","data":{"timestamp":" 946929688665"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bcdd7488-04fd-42c5-a803-0031de85a84b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929695063","data":{"timestamp":" 946929695063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bcdd7488-04fd-42c5-a803-0031de85a84b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929695649","data":{"timestamp":" 946929695649"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bcdd7488-04fd-42c5-a803-0031de85a84b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929695736","data":{"timestamp":" 946929695736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bcdd7488-04fd-42c5-a803-0031de85a84b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929713712","data":{"timestamp":" 946929713711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" bcdd7488-04fd-42c5-a803-0031de85a84b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929713830","data":{"timestamp":" 946929713829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 233f71ca-ec09-4bbb-b6eb-d7f1738f2bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929724535","data":{"timestamp":" 946929724535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 233f71ca-ec09-4bbb-b6eb-d7f1738f2bd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929737660","data":{"timestamp":" 946929737660"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c0e54b98-cfcc-4c8e-b655-96cab0dd9e3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929740608","data":{"timestamp":" 946929740608"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c0e54b98-cfcc-4c8e-b655-96cab0dd9e3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929750654","data":{"timestamp":" 946929750654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929754029","data":{"timestamp":" 946929754029"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929755613","data":{"timestamp":" 946929755613"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929759382","data":{"timestamp":" 946929759382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929760939","data":{"timestamp":" 946929760939"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929764364","data":{"timestamp":" 946929764364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929765943","data":{"timestamp":" 946929765943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929773869","data":{"timestamp":" 946929773868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929775426","data":{"timestamp":" 946929775426"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929778731","data":{"timestamp":" 946929778731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929780320","data":{"timestamp":" 946929780320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929786548","data":{"timestamp":" 946929786548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929788119","data":{"timestamp":" 946929788118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929791730","data":{"timestamp":" 946929791729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929793285","data":{"timestamp":" 946929793284"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929798055","data":{"timestamp":" 946929798055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929800060","data":{"timestamp":" 946929800060"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929800145","data":{"timestamp":" 946929800145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" c64d62d6-8410-43b3-a214-87611dcf1982"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929832843","data":{"timestamp":" 946929832843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929835931","data":{"timestamp":" 946929835930"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929837474","data":{"timestamp":" 946929837474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929840426","data":{"timestamp":" 946929840426"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929842043","data":{"timestamp":" 946929842043"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929850780","data":{"timestamp":" 946929850780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929852456","data":{"timestamp":" 946929852455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929856422","data":{"timestamp":" 946929856421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929858038","data":{"timestamp":" 946929858037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929861283","data":{"timestamp":" 946929861283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929862846","data":{"timestamp":" 946929862846"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929866072","data":{"timestamp":" 946929866072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929867670","data":{"timestamp":" 946929867670"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929870525","data":{"timestamp":" 946929870525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929872126","data":{"timestamp":" 946929872126"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929875000","data":{"timestamp":" 946929875000"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929877009","data":{"timestamp":" 946929877008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929877095","data":{"timestamp":" 946929877095"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" d08cf925-18eb-4e3c-b124-31b10667b8ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929958144","data":{"timestamp":" 946929958144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 5e9b6e9e-9c34-4b62-b03b-82852ea3a1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kelele_kelele-hii-kamba-nguo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kelele"," userResponse":" kelele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929978066","data":{"timestamp":" 946929978066"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 5e9b6e9e-9c34-4b62-b03b-82852ea3a1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwao_kadhaa-mwao-bure-tazama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mwao"," userResponse":" kadhaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929980741","data":{"timestamp":" 946929980741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 5e9b6e9e-9c34-4b62-b03b-82852ea3a1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwao_kadhaa-mwao-bure-tazama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mwao"," userResponse":" mwao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929983359","data":{"timestamp":" 946929983359"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 5e9b6e9e-9c34-4b62-b03b-82852ea3a1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mwao_kadhaa-mwao-bure-tazama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929983445","data":{"timestamp":" 946929983445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 5e9b6e9e-9c34-4b62-b03b-82852ea3a1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946929992543","data":{"timestamp":" 946929992543"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 5e9b6e9e-9c34-4b62-b03b-82852ea3a1b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini baada ya mwezi waliona wadudu shambani ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930006753","data":{"timestamp":" 946930006752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930017145","data":{"timestamp":" 946930017145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" START_UZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930019414","data":{"timestamp":" 946930019414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930020957","data":{"timestamp":" 946930020957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930023848","data":{"timestamp":" 946930023848"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930025436","data":{"timestamp":" 946930025436"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930032753","data":{"timestamp":" 946930032753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" START_UKUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930036085","data":{"timestamp":" 946930036085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930037647","data":{"timestamp":" 946930037647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930042025","data":{"timestamp":" 946930042025"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930043643","data":{"timestamp":" 946930043642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930046154","data":{"timestamp":" 946930046154"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930047760","data":{"timestamp":" 946930047760"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930049646","data":{"timestamp":" 946930049645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930049755","data":{"timestamp":" 946930049755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" beeb06e6-bfe0-4719-a5e8-36f2190b877a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930061147","data":{"timestamp":" 946930061147"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" b019e306-8ab7-4a6b-9d71-4f1308dc7c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930066506","data":{"timestamp":" 946930066506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" b019e306-8ab7-4a6b-9d71-4f1308dc7c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930084651","data":{"timestamp":" 946930084650"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" b019e306-8ab7-4a6b-9d71-4f1308dc7c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930106014","data":{"timestamp":" 946930106014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" b019e306-8ab7-4a6b-9d71-4f1308dc7c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930116581","data":{"timestamp":" 946930116580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" b019e306-8ab7-4a6b-9d71-4f1308dc7c6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930129953","data":{"timestamp":" 946930129953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930140099","data":{"timestamp":" 946930140099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930141715","data":{"timestamp":" 946930141713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930147014","data":{"timestamp":" 946930147014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930148640","data":{"timestamp":" 946930148640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930151335","data":{"timestamp":" 946930151335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930152932","data":{"timestamp":" 946930152932"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930165415","data":{"timestamp":" 946930165415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" START_UKULIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930168952","data":{"timestamp":" 946930168951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930170546","data":{"timestamp":" 946930170545"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930176120","data":{"timestamp":" 946930176120"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930177762","data":{"timestamp":" 946930177762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930192846","data":{"timestamp":" 946930192846"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930194485","data":{"timestamp":" 946930194484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930197260","data":{"timestamp":" 946930197259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930198854","data":{"timestamp":" 946930198854"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930201823","data":{"timestamp":" 946930201823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930203832","data":{"timestamp":" 946930203831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930204020","data":{"timestamp":" 946930204020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" 9f1050d4-313e-40a7-9d6b-d0c2a54fea7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930368976","data":{"timestamp":" 946930368976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930369208","data":{"timestamp":" 946930369208"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930370181","data":{"timestamp":" 946930370181"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930371463","data":{"timestamp":" 946930371463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930374435","data":{"timestamp":" 946930374434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930375315","data":{"timestamp":" 946930375315"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930375647","data":{"timestamp":" 946930375646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930376901","data":{"timestamp":" 946930376901"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930380430","data":{"timestamp":" 946930380429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930381431","data":{"timestamp":" 946930381431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930381695","data":{"timestamp":" 946930381694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930382649","data":{"timestamp":" 946930382649"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930385575","data":{"timestamp":" 946930385575"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930386634","data":{"timestamp":" 946930386633"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930387116","data":{"timestamp":" 946930387116"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930391648","data":{"timestamp":" 946930391647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946930391748","data":{"timestamp":" 946930391748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_225939"," gameId":" ef4e7586-9b15-4924-b1a4-7cca0ac638ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}